Class of 1899 Records, 1895-1964
Smith College Archives
Class of 1899 Records
1895-1964
Smith College. Class of 1899.
RG 80 UUID:0ab9d352-adef-4a4e-b7c4-7160120db93f
19 boxes (13.3 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 19 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1899.
The Class of 1899 was the twenty-first entering class and the twenty-first graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1899 records, 1895-1964, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1899, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1899 records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Service 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 1)
- Collation undated (Box 1568, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 3)
- Commencement Photos 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 4)
- Commencement Music 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 5)
- Freshman Grind by 1898 1895 (Box 1568, Folder 6)
- Groups Photos 1895-1899 (Box 1568, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 8)
- Ivy Day 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 10)
- Junior Prom 1898 (Box 1568, Folder 11)
- Letters 1914-1956 (Box 1568, Folder 12)
- Reunions undated (Box 1568, Folder 13)
- Reunion 1900 (Box 1568, Folder 14)
- Reunion 1901 (Box 1568, Folder 15)
- Reunion 1904 (Box 1568, Folder 16)
- Reunion 1909 (Box 1568, Folder 17)
- Reunion 1910 (Box 1568, Folder 18)
- Reunion 1914 (Box 1568, Folder 19)
- Reunion 1919 (Box 1569, Folder 1)
- Reunion 1924 (Box 1569, Folder 2)
- Reunion 1929 (Box 1569, Folder 3)
- Reunion 1934 (Box 1569, Folder 4)
- Reunion 1939 (Box 1569, Folder 5)
- Reunion 1944 (Box 1569, Folder 6)
- Reunion 1949 (Box 1569, Folder 7)
- Reunion 1954 (Box 1569, Folder 8)
- Reunion 1959 (Box 1569, Folder 9)
- Reunion 1964 (Box 1569, Folder 10)
- Secretary's Notebook 1895-1954 (Box 1569, Folder 11)
- Songs undated (Box 1569, Folder 12)
- Sophomore Reception 1895 (Box 1569, Folder 13)
- Sophomore-Senior Entertainment for 1897 1897 (Box 1569, Folder 14)
- Student Rooms undated (Box 1569, Folder 15)
- Class Supper 1899 (Box 1569, Folder 16)
- no box (Box 1570)
- Senior Dramatics Clippings 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics: Photographs 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics: Photograph Album 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 5)
- Banner (Box OV)